Now, let's move on to the second use I mentioned for
好 现在让我们来看看我提到的 A/A 测试的第二个用处
A/A tests, where we can estimate the variance empirically
如果我们不能进行分析计算
if we weren't able to calculate it analytically.
我们可以通过实证估计方差
I'll actually compute the standard deviation instead,
我会实际计算标准偏差
since that's the direct analog of standard error.
因为它是标准误差的直接模拟
And, I do that by taking the standard deviation
为此 我先计算最小实验的
of each of the twenty differences from the smallest experiments.
二十组差异的标准偏差
And, for that size of experiment,
在这个规模的实验中
I get that the standard deviation of the difference is 0.059.
我得到差异的标准偏差为 0.059
I can also do the same thing for each of the other experiment sizes.
我可以对每个实验规模做同样的事
I won't show that here, but, again,
我这里不会再具体展示
you can find the results in the sheet linked in the instructor's notes.
同样的 你可以在讲师注释中链接的表格中找到结果
Now, since we expect that our metric follows roughly a normal distribution,
由于我们预计指标大概为正态分布
we can compute the margin of error as the standard deviation we just
我们可以计算误差范围 用刚刚计算得到的标准偏差
calculated times the Z-square of our confidence level.
乘以置信度的 Z 分数
This is the same equation you saw for the margin of error in lesson one, but
这和你之前在第一课中看到的误差范围的等式是一样的
with the empirical standard deviation instead of the analytic standard error.
但是这里用实证的标准偏差代替了分析的标准误差
If you didn't know beforehand whether to expect your metric to follow a normal
如果你还无法预计你的指标是否为正态分布
distribution, then you might look at histograms like the ones we just looked
那你可以看一看直方图 如我们之前看的那些
at to see whether the metric looked like it followed a normal distribution.
观察指标是否符合正态分布
If we do that for the small experiment we just looked at with a 95%
如果要计算小型试验 在 95% 的置信度下
confidence level, then the margin of error comes out to 0.116.
误差范围为 0.116
Remember, if we had done this analytically, the standard error depends
要记得 如果我们通过分析完成这个任务 标准误差取决于
on the pooled probability, which will be different for each experiment.
合并概率 这在每个实验中都是不同的
That means we actually would have gotten a slightly different margin of error for
也就是说 每个实验的误差范围
each experiment.
应该有些许差别
Whereas, empirically,
然而 在实证中
we calculated one margin of error across all the experiments.
我们对所有的实验计算一个误差范围
If I do calculate the pooled probability and the pooled standard error for
如果我真的为每个实验
each experiment,
计算合并概率和合并标准误差
I see that the pooled standard error varies, but it is always close to 0.059.
我可以看到合并标准误差会有不同 但是都接近 0.059
So, we're getting roughly the same results either way.
所以 我们大概还是会得到相同的结果
But if your metric doesn't seem to follow a normal distribution,
但如果你的指标看上去不像是正态分布
then what can you do?
那你可以做什么？
Well, you can also directly estimate a confidence interval from the results of
你也可以根据 A/A 测试的结果
your A/A tests.
直接估计置信区间
This is the third use case I mentioned earlier.
这就是我之前提到的第三种使用案例
The way to do this is take all your differences and put them in order,
为此 你应使用所有的差异 按顺序把他们放一起
in our case ranging from negative 0.15 to positive 0.15.
在我们的例子中 范围为负 0.15 至正 0.15
Then if you want a 95% confidence interval,
如果你想要 95% 的置信度
select a box that includes only 95% of the values.
那你要选择一个方框 仅包括 95% 的值
That is discard 2.5% of your values on each side.
也就是在每一边舍掉 2.5% 的值
Then, the range of your remaining data points will give you a 95%
这样 剩下的数据点范围
confidence level.
让你达到 95% 的置信度
Since we have 20 data points in our smallest experiment group, dropping
由于在最小实验组中 我们有 20 个数据点
the highest and the lowest difference give us a 90% confidence interval.
去掉最大和最小差异 会得到 90% 的置信区间
For our data, that gives us a lower bound of negative 0.1, and
对我们的数据来说 也就是下限为负 0.1
an upper bound of 0.06.
上限为 0.06
Recall that the empirical standard deviation I calculated a minute ago was
回忆一下我刚刚计算的
0.059.
实证标准偏差为 0.059
Now, if I multiply that by 1.65 which is the z-score for
乘以 1.65 即 90% 置信度的 Z 分数
a 90% confidence level, then that comes to about 0.097.
结果为 0.097
So, if the true difference were 0 that would give us a confidence interval of
如果真正的差异为 0 那置信区间应该为
negative 0.097 to positive 0.097.
负 0.097 至正 0.097
So, these two methods give a sort of close answer, but it's not that close.
所以这两种方法的答案是相似的 但也不尽相同
The main reason for this is that we only have 20 data points.
重要的原因是 我们只有 20 个数据点
You'd probably want to run more A/A tests to actually trust
我们可能需要运行更多的 A/A 测试以获得可信的
this confidence interval, unless each test was run for a pretty long time.
置信区间 除非每一个测试运行的时间相当长
You also can't differentiate between a 90% confidence level and
你没有办法通过 20 次测试区分 90% 与 95% 的置信度
a 95% with only 20 tests, since the best you can do is drop the lowest point and
因为你最好去掉最低点和最高点
the highest point, which already takes you down to a 90% confidence level.
这样就会让置信度降低至 90%